<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Germany on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/categories/germany/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Germany on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/categories/germany/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April Garden Update During COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one month since Germany closed its borders to neighboring countries, one month since we’ve been able to visit the Kleingarten located only 200m (660ft) in Switzerland. It’s a little sad not being able to observe the garden transition into spring. Around this time of year the fruit trees are blooming and it’s the perfect time to celebrate spring by cooking food over a fire. We were lucky enough to enjoy a small picnic, with proper social distancing of course, under the flowering plum tree the day before the closing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges with the German Language</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/learning-german/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 13:21:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/learning-german/</guid>
      <description>Steigstraße
  Living in Germany has its difficulties, particularly as a non-native speaker. In an ideal world I would be able to find everything I need to apply what I preach, but that can be challenging. The most obvious hurdle is language. I don’t know all the German terminology associated with gardening; it’s learn-as-you-go. This can be annoying since I don’t even possess the common knowledge of where to find certain products like I do in the States, not to mention not knowing the names of the products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 12:40:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</guid>
      <description>Fahrradstraße, or &amp;#39;bike street&amp;#39;
  Bicycling is one of my favorite things about living in Germany. There are clearly-marked lanes specifically for bicyclists and should you accidently wander into one, you will be reminded by angry shouts and ringing bells, or simply run over.
Motorists, the majority of the time, are fairly respectful of bikes, at least in the city I live in. But there is one major downside when you don’t have a car and that is space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>