<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Balkongarten on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/categories/balkongarten/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Balkongarten on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/categories/balkongarten/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April Garden Update During COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one month since Germany closed its borders to neighboring countries, one month since we’ve been able to visit the Kleingarten located only 200m (660ft) in Switzerland. It’s a little sad not being able to observe the garden transition into spring. Around this time of year the fruit trees are blooming and it’s the perfect time to celebrate spring by cooking food over a fire. We were lucky enough to enjoy a small picnic, with proper social distancing of course, under the flowering plum tree the day before the closing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Balkongarten Reflection</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/balkongarten-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 09:32:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/balkongarten-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Balkongarten in August
  I think it’s important to reflect on the successes and failures of the 2019 Balkongarten. Taking a few moments to reflect will help me realize where to focus my efforts next season in order to grow as a gardner. Be sure to take some time to reflect on your growing season or, if you’re new to gardening, imagine what you’d like to accomplish for your first season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Flower of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:42:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</guid>
      <description>I want to talk about a flower I fell in love with growing this year. It’s called Tithonia rotundifolia, commonly known as Mexican Sunflower or Rundblättrige Tithonie in German. There are many things about this plant that I love, but the main reason is that it&amp;rsquo;s easy to grow from seed and very forgiving, so beginner balcony growers take note!
   First bloom opening up for the season</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving the Gift that Grows</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/plants-as-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:34:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/plants-as-gifts/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few years I’ve been changing my gift-giving game. I used to give generic items that people might like but might not be useful to them. When receiving items like this I thought, “if I don’t like receiving gifts like this then why should I give them?” It’s a waste of money and the person is stuck trying to figure out what to do with it. I’ve changed my mindset to giving things that I know they need/want, are useful, something enjoyable, or money when nothing fits the above criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: The Scary Seed</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 08:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
My latest article is an overview of how to sow seeds. So if you’re like me and are a little intimidated by seeds, then this is the read for you. In it, you’ll learn the basics of what seeds need in order to survive. Happy planting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June Update</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 09:46:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</guid>
      <description>This is the craziest time of the year for gardeners. Everything is growing so fast that we can’t keep up. For a while I managed to keep on top of everything but now I’m falling behind, in both the Kleingarten and my Balkongarten. The most pressing jobs in the Kleingarten, such as the grapevine roof trellis and winter rye cutting, are completed on time, but the balcony has taken a back seat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>