<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 16:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges with the German Language</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/2018-08-06-netlify-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/2018-08-06-netlify-test/</guid>
      <description>Living in Germany has its difficulties, particularly as a non-native speaker. In an ideal world I would be able to find and apply everything I preach but that can be challenging. The most obvious is language. I don’t know all the German terminology associated with gardening; it’s learn-as-you-go. This can be annoying since I don’t even possess the common knowledge of where to find certain products like I do in the States, not to mention not knowing the names of the products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Here&#39;s the Dill!</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jayme and I recently discovered my passion for gardening or rather in plants and their interactions within the world.
   Säntis Switzerland Hike   I studied biology with a specialization in marine and aquatic biology thinking I wanted to research coral reef ecosystems— thank you Blue Planet and Discovery Channel. But it wasn’t until I started moving further away from home that I realized what I my true interests were, digging in the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 12:40:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</guid>
      <description>Bicycling is one of my favorite things about living in Germany. There are clearly marked lanes specifically for bicyclists and should you accidently wander into one you will be reminded by angry shouts and ringing bells or- simply run over.
Motorists, the majority of the time, are fairly respectful of bikes at least in the city I live in. But there is one major downside when you don’t have a car and that is space and weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall is here, with a new article!</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/soil-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:22:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/soil-intro/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing week! The weather finally turned here in Konstanz: the temperature is dropping, the leaves are changing—Herbst hat angekommen! I snapped a photo for you below!
Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a new series of articles about soil, and I just posted the first one! You can read it here!
  View this post on Instagram        Autumn colors in the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>