<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seeds on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/categories/seeds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seeds on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 08:21:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/categories/seeds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: The Scary Seed</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 08:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
My latest article is an overview of how to sow seeds. So if you’re like me and are a little intimidated by seeds, then this is the read for you. In it, you’ll learn the basics of what seeds need in order to survive. Happy planting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scary Seed</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:34:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/seeds/</guid>
      <description>This is the year, the year that I’m finally going to face a fear. In the past I’ve avoided it and paid the price. It’s the seed.
 Tithonia seedlings I forgot to water; luckily they sprung back after a good soak.
  That’s right, I’ve been afraid of starting from seed. Who wants to get their hopes up watching their tiny seedlings grow, only to see them die later?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: Starting your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 08:14:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
If you haven’t done so, check out my Articles section for Starting Your Seed Calendar. It’ll teach you how to create an outline of when to sow seeds so you don’t miss crucial planting windows in your specific climate. It’s a great way to stay organized and keep records for present and future growing seasons. Be sure to post your photo on twitter with #seedcalendar and @hereisthedill!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Greenhouse</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/desktop-greenhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:57:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/desktop-greenhouse/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about gardening is the creative opportunity to construct something when the need arises. While cleaning out a storage closet at work I came across an aquarium and an aquarium light.
Now, my job involves working with fish so this equipment is useful but this aquarium is missing a side panel: not very useful for holding water anymore. This particular aquarium light is not used in the lab anymore either so these items were destined for the Auspackraum, the recycling / trash room within the University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 17:37:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</guid>
      <description>I think everyone loves the idea of growing from seed but most people are afraid to do it. It’s time to get over that fear—me included—mainly because they are much cheaper than buying plants at the store and are much more rewarding. There are also more varieties to choose from than what you’ll find in stores. But before you plant seeds it’s best to know when to plant them for the most success, and this is where a seed calendar comes in handy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>