<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 09:07:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Journal</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/garden-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 09:07:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/garden-journal/</guid>
      <description>Bonus: stickers can be used to personalize it! This one&amp;#39;s from the Herdhover project, a friend of HTD!
  During my final years at college, I created a crude version of a bullet journal to keep track of all the various classes and activities. That planner was a life saver. Post college I stopped using the planner as the activity level dropped; but in the past few years, I found myself needing to record events and thoughts again, and came across bullet journaling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildflower Meadow Project</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/meadows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 10:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/meadows/</guid>
      <description>The best and worst thing about gardening is the wait. In today’s world of instant gratification many would argue it’s always the worst, but gardening is more about observing and enjoying the process rather than the end result. Unfortunately, there are projects that are oh-so-difficult to wait for. I’ve been dreaming up a wildflower meadow project since May of last year, patiently waiting for autumn to arrive in order to start it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Balkongarten Reflection</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/balkongarten-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 09:32:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/balkongarten-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Balkongarten in August
  I think it’s important to reflect on the successes and failures of the 2019 Balkongarten. Taking a few moments to reflect will help me realize where to focus my efforts next season in order to grow as a gardner. Be sure to take some time to reflect on your growing season or, if you’re new to gardening, imagine what you’d like to accomplish for your first season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Flower of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:42:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</guid>
      <description>I want to talk about a flower I fell in love with growing this year. It’s called Tithonia rotundifolia, commonly known as Mexican Sunflower or Rundblättrige Tithonie in German. There are many things about this plant that I love, but the main reason is that it&amp;rsquo;s easy to grow from seed and very forgiving, so beginner balcony growers take note!
   First bloom opening up for the season</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving the Gift that Grows</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/plants-as-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:34:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/plants-as-gifts/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few years I’ve been changing my gift-giving game. I used to give generic items that people might like but might not be useful to them. When receiving items like this I thought, “if I don’t like receiving gifts like this then why should I give them?” It’s a waste of money and the person is stuck trying to figure out what to do with it. I’ve changed my mindset to giving things that I know they need/want, are useful, something enjoyable, or money when nothing fits the above criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gardener&#39;s Fall</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/gardeners-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:36:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/gardeners-fall/</guid>
      <description>First video created! Wishing all the gardeners&amp;rsquo; out there a wonderful season as they prepare for spring. Enjoy!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: The Scary Seed</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 08:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/seed-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
My latest article is an overview of how to sow seeds. So if you’re like me and are a little intimidated by seeds, then this is the read for you. In it, you’ll learn the basics of what seeds need in order to survive. Happy planting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scary Seed</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:34:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/seeds/</guid>
      <description>This is the year, the year that I’m finally going to face a fear. In the past I’ve avoided it and paid the price. It’s the seed.
 Tithonia seedlings I forgot to water; luckily they sprung back after a good soak.
  That’s right, I’ve been afraid of starting from seed. Who wants to get their hopes up watching their tiny seedlings grow, only to see them die later?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June Update</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 09:46:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</guid>
      <description>This is the craziest time of the year for gardeners. Everything is growing so fast that we can’t keep up. For a while I managed to keep on top of everything but now I’m falling behind, in both the Kleingarten and my Balkongarten. The most pressing jobs in the Kleingarten, such as the grapevine roof trellis and winter rye cutting, are completed on time, but the balcony has taken a back seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges with the German Language</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/learning-german/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 13:21:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/learning-german/</guid>
      <description>Steigstraße
  Living in Germany has its difficulties, particularly as a non-native speaker. In an ideal world I would be able to find everything I need to apply what I preach, but that can be challenging. The most obvious hurdle is language. I don’t know all the German terminology associated with gardening; it’s learn-as-you-go. This can be annoying since I don’t even possess the common knowledge of where to find certain products like I do in the States, not to mention not knowing the names of the products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: Starting your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 08:14:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
If you haven’t done so, check out my Articles section for Starting Your Seed Calendar. It’ll teach you how to create an outline of when to sow seeds so you don’t miss crucial planting windows in your specific climate. It’s a great way to stay organized and keep records for present and future growing seasons. Be sure to post your photo on twitter with #seedcalendar and @hereisthedill!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Greenhouse</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/desktop-greenhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:57:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/desktop-greenhouse/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about gardening is the creative opportunity to construct something when the need arises. While cleaning out a storage closet at work I came across an aquarium and an aquarium light.
Now, my job involves working with fish so this equipment is useful but this aquarium is missing a side panel: not very useful for holding water anymore. This particular aquarium light is not used in the lab anymore either so these items were destined for the Auspackraum, the recycling / trash room within the University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 12:40:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/cycling/</guid>
      <description>Fahrradstraße, or &amp;#39;bike street&amp;#39;
  Bicycling is one of my favorite things about living in Germany. There are clearly-marked lanes specifically for bicyclists and should you accidently wander into one, you will be reminded by angry shouts and ringing bells, or simply run over.
Motorists, the majority of the time, are fairly respectful of bikes, at least in the city I live in. But there is one major downside when you don’t have a car and that is space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 17:37:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</guid>
      <description>I think everyone loves the idea of growing from seed but most people are afraid to do it. It’s time to get over that fear—me included—mainly because they are much cheaper than buying plants at the store and are much more rewarding. There are also more varieties to choose from than what you’ll find in stores. But before you plant seeds it’s best to know when to plant them for the most success, and this is where a seed calendar comes in handy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Here&#39;s the Dill!</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jayme and I recently discovered my passion for gardening, or rather, in plants and their interactions within the world.
I studied biology with a specialization in marine and aquatic biology thinking I wanted to research coral reef ecosystems—thank you Blue Planet and Discovery Channel. But it wasn’t until I started moving further away from home that I realized what my true interests were: digging in the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 12:03:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in either Germany or the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage. We do not sell, share, or distribute this anonymized data in any way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 10:09:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions or comments, please reach out! I love connecting with other gardeners and like-minded people around the globe!
You can find me on Twitter or Instagram, or email me directly at hereisthedill@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 09:57:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/glossary/</guid>
      <description>der Auspackraum: an amazing room in the University where you can go dumpster diving sort trash to be reused or recycled. Every university should have one.
die Blumenzwiebel: spring bulb, literal translation flowering bulb
der Chef: the boss, owner of the garden
der Garten des Chefs: the boss’s garden, literal translation ‘the garden of the boss’ aka a pain in the butt grammar rule called Genitive, denoting possession
Steigstrasse: ‘climb street,’ a very steep street in Meersburg which requires climbing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 15:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Me!
  Hi! I’m Jayme, an American expat sharpening her organic gardening and German language skills in beautiful southern Germany. I started gardening at age 10 when my dad dug an egg-shaped garden bed for me out of the lawn one rainy April morning in 2001—that’s true love right there!
Since then I studied biology, expanded my gardening knowledge and bed by stealing one of my mom’s neighboring gardening beds—also true love—and interned for a summer on an organic farm in Northeast Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>