<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 16:04:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 10:09:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions or comments, please reach out! I love connecting with other gardeners and like-minded people around the globe!
You can find me on Twitter or Instagram, or email me directly at hereisthedill@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 09:57:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/glossary/</guid>
      <description>die Blumenzwiebel: spring bulb, literal translation flowering bulb [P1]
der Chef: the boss, owner of the garden [A1 Intro]
der Garten des Chefs: the boss’s garden, literal translation ‘the garden of the boss’ aka a pain in the butt grammar rule called Genitive, denoting possession [About]
Steigstrasse: ‘climb street,’ a very steep street in Meersburg which requires climbing [P1]
der Fingerhut: foxglove, literal translation finger hat Digitalis purpurea [P1]
die Fruehlingszwiebel: green onion, spring onion [P1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Here&#39;s the Dill!</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jayme and I recently discovered my passion for gardening or rather in plants and their interactions within the world.
I studied biology with a specialization in marine and aquatic biology thinking I wanted to research coral reef ecosystems— thank you Blue Planet and Discovery Channel. But it wasn’t until I started moving further away from home that I realized what I my true interests were, digging in the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 15:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I’m Jayme, an American expat sharpening her organic gardening and German language skills in beautiful southern Germany. I started gardening at age 10 when my dad dug an egg-shaped garden bed for me out of the lawn one rainy April morning in 2001—that’s true love right there!
Since then I studied biology, expanded my gardening knowledge and bed by stealing one of my mom’s neighboring gardening beds—also true love—and interned for a summer on an organic farm in Northeast Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>