<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/categories/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/categories/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April Garden Update During COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:06:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/covid-update/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one month since Germany closed its borders to neighboring countries, one month since we’ve been able to visit the Kleingarten located only 200m (660ft) in Switzerland. It’s a little sad not being able to observe the garden transition into spring. Around this time of year the fruit trees are blooming and it’s the perfect time to celebrate spring by cooking food over a fire. We were lucky enough to enjoy a small picnic, with proper social distancing of course, under the flowering plum tree the day before the closing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Flower of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:42:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/tithonia/</guid>
      <description>I want to talk about a flower I fell in love with growing this year. It’s called Tithonia rotundifolia, commonly known as Mexican Sunflower or Rundblättrige Tithonie in German. There are many things about this plant that I love, but the main reason is that it&amp;rsquo;s easy to grow from seed and very forgiving, so beginner balcony growers take note!
   First bloom opening up for the season</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June Update</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 09:46:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/june-update/</guid>
      <description>This is the craziest time of the year for gardeners. Everything is growing so fast that we can’t keep up. For a while I managed to keep on top of everything but now I’m falling behind, in both the Kleingarten and my Balkongarten. The most pressing jobs in the Kleingarten, such as the grapevine roof trellis and winter rye cutting, are completed on time, but the balcony has taken a back seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Here&#39;s the Dill!</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/launch/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jayme and I recently discovered my passion for gardening, or rather, in plants and their interactions within the world.
I studied biology with a specialization in marine and aquatic biology thinking I wanted to research coral reef ecosystems—thank you Blue Planet and Discovery Channel. But it wasn’t until I started moving further away from home that I realized what my true interests were: digging in the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>