<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organization on Here&#39;s the Dill</title>
    <link>https://hereisthedill.com/categories/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organization on Here&#39;s the Dill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 09:07:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hereisthedill.com/categories/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Journal</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/garden-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 09:07:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/garden-journal/</guid>
      <description>During my final years at college, I created a crude version of a bullet journal to keep track of all the various classes and activities. That planner was a life saver. Post college I stopped using the planner as the activity level dropped; but in the past few years, I found myself needing to record events and thoughts again, and came across bullet journaling. It has really helped keep life organized, so in the spirit of staying organized, I decided to create a garden journal using the same techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Article: Starting your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 08:14:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/posts/calendar-blurb/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone!
If you haven’t done so, check out my Articles section for Starting Your Seed Calendar. It’ll teach you how to create an outline of when to sow seeds so you don’t miss crucial planting windows in your specific climate. It’s a great way to stay organized and keep records for present and future growing seasons. Be sure to post your photo on twitter with #seedcalendar and @hereisthedill!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Your Seed Calendar</title>
      <link>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 17:37:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hereisthedill.com/articles/starting-your-seed-calendar/</guid>
      <description>I think everyone loves the idea of growing from seed but most people are afraid to do it. It’s time to get over that fear—me included—mainly because they are much cheaper than buying plants at the store and are much more rewarding. There are also more varieties to choose from than what you’ll find in stores. But before you plant seeds it’s best to know when to plant them for the most success, and this is where a seed calendar comes in handy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>